http://www.aptv.org/about/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
About APTAwardsBoard of DirectorsBroadcast ChannelsCommunity Services ReportContact UsDirectionsDiversity PlanDownload Monthly GuideEmploymentFCC Public InspectionFinancial StatementsHistoryInternshipsMission StatementPBS ValuePrivacy PolicyPressroomStaff Directory
About Menu
About APTAwardsBoard of DirectorsBroadcast ChannelsCommunity Services ReportContact UsDirectionsDiversity PlanDownload Monthly GuideEmploymentFCC Public InspectionFinancial StatementsHistoryInternshipsMission StatementPBS ValuePrivacy PolicyPressroomStaff Directory
Go
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is of utmost importance to Alabama Public Television.  To maintain the trust you have in us, we pledge to make our Web site a safe and secure environment.  This privacy policy will advise you on information we collect about you and how we may use that information.  Our priority is to take all steps necessary to ensure the security of your information.
Gathering and Use of Information
We do not collect any personal identification information from you other than what you supply voluntarily.  Anyone under the age of 13 must have their parents’ approval before sending APT any personal identification information.
We may ask you to submit personal identification information to include your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number if needed to provide you with specific services.  These may include your subscription to our electronic newsletter, purchasing products, requesting information or making an initial or renewal contribution to APT.  In those cases, we will ask only for the information necessary.  We will also advise you as to how the information will be used and, whenever possible, provide an alternate way of participating that preserves your online anonymity.
We do not sell or trade personal identification information about our users. The only outside parties with whom this information is shared are those hired by APT to complete a transaction in which you have chosen to participate, such as fulfilling your request for a thank-you gift or with an outside supplier who provides mail services for our organization.  APT’s contracts with such organizations stipulate that they cannot use the information provided for any use other than the intended use.
APT may occasionally use some of the personal identification information you furnish to advise you about educational, fundraising, or broadcast programs or services in which you may have indicated an interest.  For example, we may remind you when your membership is about to lapse, or we may use it to notify you of something you need to know to ensure uninterrupted service from APT. You will always have the option to “opt out” of a service or subscription, which will be honored as quickly as possible.
Credit Card Information
Only individuals age 18 or older may make credit card transactions with APT. All financial transactions made online take place on secure servers and are sent only in a secured or encrypted format.  Personal credit card information is saved in an encrypted format on internal systems that are either not connected to the Internet or are protected by advanced firewalls that are separate from the computers that serve APT public sites.  As with other personal identification information gathered by APT, this information is not made available to any third party and is considered completely confidential.  When you join APT, your name, complete contact information, and all contributions are received by APT’s Membership Department, where the information is fully protected.
Tracking and Use of Cookies
In order to allow you to customize certain areas of our Web site, such as the TV schedules, or to complete a transaction, at times we will store a “cookie” on your computer.  This small text file records a randomly generated ID for you, along with the data necessary to maintain the level of customization you have selected.
APT’s Web site also uses cookies to collect anonymous data about visits to certain areas of the site.  These cookies contain no personal identification information.  They simply record patterns of usage of the Web site so that we may monitor its performance and continue to improve its usefulness to visitors.
Acceptance of APT Online Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions
By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of APT’s Online Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site.  We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add to, or remove portions of this policy at any time to further enhance its usefulness.  Please check this page periodically for any changes.  Your continued use of the APT Web site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes.
If you have any questions or concerns about APT’s privacy policy or practices on APT’s Web site, please e-mail us at webmaster@aptv.org, or write to:  APT Webmaster, 2112 11th Avenue South, Suite 400, Birmingham, AL  35205-2884.
Contact
Phone: 800-239-5233
Alabama Public Television
2112 11th Ave South, Suite 400
Birmingham, AL 35205
View map
Directions
Explore
Federal Tax ID: 63-6000619
Alabama Public Television is committed to enriching the lives of Alabama citizens and is made possible through the support of the State of Alabama and viewers like you. © 2020 All Rights Reserved.
Follow Us
Visit Alabama Public Television Facebook Page
Alabama Public Television Twitter Feed
Visit Alabama Public Television YouTube Page
Visit Alabama Public Television Instagram Channel
EEO Public File Vacancies/Outreach Initiatives  |  Diversity Report/Plan  |   Public Inspection Files  |  Privacy Policy
